<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Chris Turner</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Chris Turner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Inference, Prediction</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Jocelyn Harnold (jh67282)
Introduction My dataset is called HI or Health Insurance and Hours Worked By Wives. The main variables used in this project is whrswk, hhi, whi, hhi2, education, race, hispanic, experience, kidslt6, kids618, husby, and region. The numeric variables include whrswk measures the hours worked per week, experience which states each wife&#39;s years of potential work experience, and husby which is the husband&#39;s income in thousands of dollars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Wrangling &amp; Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Jocelyn Harnold (jh67282)
Introduction During the last few semesters as a pre-health student, I have become more and more invested in upstream factors that affect health throughout the world. One of the most well-known poisons to our bodies is alcohol. I want to compare the life-expectancies to the amount of alcohol consumed per person for each country recorded in 2010. The dataset,&amp;quot;drinks&amp;quot;, records the amount of beer, wine, and spirits consumed per person in each country in 2010 and was taken from the R-package &amp;quot;fivethirtyeight&amp;quot; while the original data was collected from the World Health Organization.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
